Register to The Harold Rome Papers
Yale University Music Library
- Music by Rome, 1935-1981; Series I; 24.2' (58 boxes)
  - Stage Works, I.A
    - [Southpaw] Southpaw / Words and Music by Harold Rome. -- ca. 1969 Jan. 13., 1 manuscript score (74 p. in various pagings); 32 cm. (Box 41, Folder 290)
      Contents [in order in which they were found]: You get in my way. Futz around. Gimme a ball in my hand. The boss. There's only one game. Holly. Mary Pistologione. Henry. As I was remarking. You get in my way. Rosy. Passing through. Love that game. Which is which. Bloody finger. Girls. Katie. The good samaritan
    - [Southpaw] Southpaw / Words and Music by Harold Rome. -- 1969 Jan. 27., 1 manuscript score (82 p. in various pagings), bound; 33 cm. (Box 41, Folder 291)
      Note on cover: preliminary rehearsal score Jan. 27, 1969
      Scores (holographs, signed, in pencil) for "Love the game intro" and "Swat that fly" with lyrics (2 sheets; typescript) laid in
      Contents: Gimme a ball in my hand. Futz around. The boss. You get in my way. The good samaritan. Katie. Love that game. Which is which. Girls. Rosy. Bloody finger. Mary Pistologione. Passing through. As I was remarking.
    - [Southpaw] The game / Harold Rome., 1 manuscript score (96 p. in various pagings), bound; 33 cm. (Box 41, Folder 292)
      Contents: Let's go Mammoths. Intro to Love the game. Love the game. Bloody finger. I'm gonna work your tails off. A friend is a friend. Only passing through. Apologizn' blues. Katie. I lust for you. Hall of fame. Henry. Henry - Interlude. Bruce William Pearson, Junior. The Washington fly. Girls. Again. The world is so rosy. Pretty Penny. Mary Pistologione. What a game is all about.
    - [Southpaw. Only yesterday] Only yesterday / Florence and Harold. -- c1981., 1 manuscript score (3 p.); 32 cm. (Box 41, Folder 293)
      For voice and piano
    - [Southpaw. Selections], 1968 Apr.-Dec; 1 manuscript score (116 p. in various pagings); 31 cm. (Box 41, Folder 294)
      Includes sketches and lyrics ([68] sheets; holographs in pencil and typescript)
    - [Southpaw. Selections], ca. 1978 Jul. 4; 1 manuscript score (149 p. in various pagings); 32 cm. (Box 42, Folder 295-296)
      Holographs, signed, in pencil and ink and manuscript (photocopies) with pencil additions
      Includes sketches and lyrics ([4] sheets; typescript)
      Note on discarded folder: Southpaw Music + Lyrics mostly discarded
    - [Southpaw (Sketches)], 1962-1967; [162] p. of music; 31 cm. (Box 42, Folder 297-299)
      Includes scores for voice and piano and lyrics ([176] sheets; holographs in pencil and typescript)
      Note on discarded envelope: Work sheets 1966-Mar 1967 Wonderful Door / Southpaw
    - [Southpaw (Sketches)], 1966-1967; [109] p. of music; 32 cm. (Box 43, Folder 300)
      Includes scores for voice with piano and lyrics ([63] sheets; holographs in pencil and typescript)
      Note on discarded envelope: original manuscripts and work sheets
    - [Southpaw (Sketches)], 1967-1968; [139] p. of music; 31 cm. (Box 43, Folder 301-302)
      Holographs, signed, in pencil and manuscript (photocopy)
      Includes scores for voice with piano, and lyrics ([139] sheets; holographs in pencil and typescript)
      Note on discarded envelope: Work sheets from Dec 1967 to June 1968
    - [Stars and gripes. The little brown suit my uncle bought me] The Little Brown Suit My Uncle Bought Me: From Ft. Hamilton all Soldier Show "Stars and Gripes" / Words and Music by Harold Rome. -- N.Y.: Leeds Music Corporation, c1943., 1 score (5 p.); 31 cm. (Box 43, Folder 303)
    - [That's the ticket] That's the ticket / Harold Rome. -- ca. 1948., 1 manuscript score (436 p. in various pagings) + 21 parts; 32-37 cm. (Box 43, Folder 304-330, Box 44, Box 45)
      Contents [arranged according to the conductor's part, with the numbers not appearing in the part at the end]: Intro. to Opening. #1 Opening. Entrance of Alfrog. Act I - Scene II. #2 Looking for a candidate. Alfred's fanfare. Read all about it. Clank, clank! Clank tag. The ballad of Marcia Larue. You never know what hit you. Misterioso #1. Misterioso #2. Intro. to Dost thou. Dost thou. #12 Campaign song. Finale act I. Temp. entr'acte. Cry baby. I shouldn't love you. The fair sex. Temp. overture. Political lady utility. Determined woman. The five knights. Finale ultimo. Final bows. Newsreel. [the following numbers are not in order] Paste job temp. ove. Living room fanfare. Love is still love. Political lady.
      List of musical numbers (typescript) laid in with many parts
    - [That's the ticket. Fanfare] Fanfare., 19 manuscript parts; 32 cm. (Box 46, Folder 331)
      Includes a conductor's part, trumpet, trombone, and drum parts, and 14 tacet parts
    - [That's the ticket. Love is still love] Love is still love., 20 manuscript parts; 32 cm. (Box 46, Folder 332)
      Duplicates (photocopies) laid in
    - [That's the ticket. The money song; arr.] The money song / Words and Music by Harold Rome; Arrangement by Geo. N. Terry. -- N.Y.: Crawford Music Corporation, c1948., 19 parts; 27 cm. (Box 46, Folder 333)
      Arranged for dance orchestra
    - [That's the ticket. The money song; arr.] The money song: Fox trot From the Musical Comedy "That's the Ticket!" / Words and Music by Harold Rome; Dance Orch. Arrangement by Jack Mason. -- N.Y.: Crawford Music Corporation, c1948., 17 parts; 27 cm. (Box 46, Folder 333)
    - [That's the ticket. Selections], c1948; 6 manuscript parts; 32 cm. (Box 46, Folder 337)
      Manuscript in ink and pencil (in part, photocopies)
      Miscellaneous parts, stickers glued to the drums part
      List of musical numbers laid in (typescript)
    - [That's the ticket. Selections], 1 manuscript score ([84] p.); 32 cm. (Box 46, Folder 334)
      Holographs, in part signed, in pencil and red pencil
      Lyrics ([25] sheets; typescript with pencil additions) laid in
      Several items labeled "Alfred the Average"
      Note on discarded folder: originals That's the Ticket
    - [That's the ticket. Selections. Vocal score], c1948; 1 manuscript vocal score ([70] p.); 22-32 cm. (Box 46, Folder 335)
      Holographs in pencil and manuscript in pencil (in part, photocopies)
      Photocopies of manuscript vocal scores labeled "Alfred the Average"
      Discarded folder and several of the musical numbers labeled "Kingsley" - possibly this was the pianist since they were marked for performance
      Includes published music
    - [That's the ticket. Selections. Vocal score], c1948; 1 manuscript vocal score (67 p. in various pagings); 16-32 cm. (Box 46, Folder 336)
      Includes duplicates, sketches, published music, and notes, some labeled "Alfred the Average"
      Possibly a pianist's part because it is marked for performance
      Discarded envelope labeled "Ray Barr"
    - [That's the ticket. Vocal score] That's the ticket / Words and music by Harold Rome. -- N.Y.: Chappell & Co., c1948., 1 manuscript vocal score (68 p. in various pagings), bound; 34 cm. (Box 46, Folder 338)
      Manuscript (photocopy), signed, with pencil additions
      Title from cover, score labeled "Alfred the Average"
      Note on p. 1: Lehman Engel
      Contents: No. 1 Opening. No. 2 Looking for a candidate. No. 4 Read all about it. No. 6 The ballad of Marcia Larue. No. 9 Dost thou. No. 10 The money song. No. 7 You never know what hit you. No. 12 Campaign song. No. 13 Newsreel. No. 16 I shouldn't love you. No. 15 Political lady. No. 17 A determined woman.
    - [That's the ticket. You never know what hit you. Vocal score] You Never Know What Hit You (When It's Love) / Words and Music by Harold Rome. -- N.Y.: Crawford Music Corporation, c1948., 1 vocal score (7 p.); 30 cm. (Box 46, Folder 339)
      With chord symbols
      Pl. no.: 1588-6
      Two copies, one missing cover
    - [That's the ticket. You never know (utility)] You Never Know (Utility)., 20 manuscript parts; 32 cm. (Box 46, Folder 340)
    - [Toujours forever. How] How / Harold Rome., 1 manuscript score (3 p.); 32 cm. (Box 46, Folder 341)
      Possibly from In the Pink?
    - [Toujours forever. Selections], 1967 Aug.-Oct; 1 manuscript score ([58] p.); 31 cm. (Box 46, Folder 342)
      Includes pencil sketches, lyrics ([41] sheets; typescript and holographs in pencil), an article about Revlon, and color lists for Revlon makeup
      Some items and discarded binder labeled IN THE PINK
    - [Toujours forever. Selections], ca. 1967 Nov. 28; 1 manuscript score ([72] p.); 32 cm. (Box 46, Folder 343)
      Manuscript in ink on onionskin (in part, photocopies) and manuscript in pencil
      Note on discarded folder: Toujours - Record Deshons
    - [Toujours forever. Selections], 1967-1968; 1 manuscript score (37 p. in various pagings); 32 cm. (Box 47, Folder 344)
      Note on discarded envelope: Discarded versions of songs 1967-1968
    - [Toujours forever. Selections], 1 manuscript score ([48] p.); 32 cm. (Box 47, Folder 345)
      Lyrics ([23] sheets; typescript) laid in
    - [Toujours forever (Sketches)], 1967-1968; [45] p. of music; 32 cm. (Box 47, Folder 346-347)
      Holographs in pencil and manuscript (photocopies) with pencil additions
      Includes manuscript scores (photocopies) for voice with piano accompaniment and lyrics
      Note on discarded folder: work sheets from Dec. 1967-June 1968
    - [Waltz of love], 1978 Feb.-Dec; 1 manuscript score (74 p. in various pagings); 32 cm. (Box 47, Folder 348)
      Holographs, signed, in pencil and manuscript (photocopies) with pencil additions
      Note on discarded envelope: Waltz originals
      Contents [in order in which it was found]: Waltz (Zing! Zing! Zing!). Inside your head. Women. Oui, Oui Papa. Time is a thief, sir. The seventeen year tango. Where is the man I used to know. Pills. Last night. Don't go to strangers. Bittersweet. Albert. Albert ["Henry" from SOUTHPAW replaced by "Albert"]. Nutshell. Intro to Nutshell. Time is a friend [note: "You're mine / Corr. 12/20/78 LJB]. He touched me. Now [note: "You're mine / Corr. 12.20/78 LJB]. Shakespeare [note: "You're mine"]. Bugle call ragout. Make way [note: Corr. 1/8/78 LJB]. The things I did not do [note: Corr. 1/8/78 LJB]
    - [Waltz of love], ca. 1979 Oct. 28; 1 manuscript score (70 p. in various pagings); 33 cm. (Box 47, Folder 349)
      Includes sketches ([14] p.; holographs, signed, in pencil) and lyrics ([2] sheets; typescript)
      Contents [in order in which it was found]: Waltz (Zing! Zing! Zing!). Inside your head. Oui, oui Papa. Time is a Thief, Sir. Seventeen Long Years. Bugle Call Ragout. Make Way For The Young. Where Is The Man I Used To Know. Pills. Last Night. Bittersweet. Albert. Nutshell. He Touched Me. The Things I Did Not Do. Women! Shakespeare. Time Is A Friend (Of New Lovers). When One and One Make One. [sketches]; Forget you. Women. Make way. The things I did not do.
    - [Waltz of love. Bittersweet] Bittersweet / Harold Rome., 1 manuscript score ([3] p.); 32 cm. (Box 47, Folder 350)
    - [Waltz of love (Sketches)], 1974 Aug.-Nov; [191] p. of music; 32 cm. (Box 48, Folder 351-353)
      Includes scores for voice with piano accompaniment, one of which, "The world is a bundle of wonderful things," is dated 1963 Dec. 11
      Also includes lyrics ([115] sheets; holographs in pencil and typescript)
      Note on discarded envelope: work sheets Waltz 1974
    - [Waltz of love (Sketches)], 1974-1975; [200] p. of music; 33 cm. (Box 48, Folder 354-356)
      Holographs, signed, in pencil (in part, photocopies)
      Includes scores for voice with piano accompaniment and lyrics ([107] sheets; holographs in pencil and typescript)
      Note on discarded envelope: work sheets Waltz 74
    - [Waltz of love (Sketches)], 1976-1979; [402] p. of music; 32 cm. (Box 49, Folder 357-361)
      Holographs, signed, in pencil and manuscript (photocopies)
      Includes scores for voice with piano accompaniment and lyrics ([32] sheets; holographs in pencil and typescript)
    - [Wee bit o'scotch. Better off] Better off / Harold Rome. -- 1970 Oct., 1 manuscript score (8 p.); 31 cm. (Box 50, Folder 362)
    - [Wee bit o'scotch. Selections], 1 manuscript score ([64] p.); 32 cm. (Box 50, Folder 363)
      Holographs, signed, in pencil and ink
      Includes sketches and lyrics ([5] sheets; typescript)
      Note on discarded folder: Engaged originals title changed to A Wee Bit O'Scotch
    - [Wee bit o'scotch (Sketches)], 1970-1971; [119] p. of music; 32 cm. (Box 50, Folder 364-366)
      Includes scores for voice with piano accompaniment and lyrics ([104] sheets; holographs in pencil)
      Note on discarded envelope: Engaged - work sheets Dec. 1970 - Apr 1971; June 1970 - work sheets
    - [Wee bit o'scotch. Together is better] Together is better / Harold Rome. -- 1970 Oct. 29., 1 manuscript score (3 p.); 34 cm. (Box 50, Folder 367)
      With: Together (Patter). -- 1970 Nov. 13; (5 p.; holograph in pencil)
    - [Wish you were here] Wish you were here / Harold Rome. -- 1951-1954., 1 manuscript score (186 p. in various pagings); 31 cm. (Box 50, Folder 368-369)
      Holograph signed, in pencil
      Includes sketches and lyrics ([8] sheets; typescript)
      Note on discarded folders: Wish You Were Here originals
      Contents [in the order in which they were found]: 2b Teddy Stern. 22 Such a nice girl! Two little schnooks in love. Two little schnooks (still in love). Two little schnooks in love. 9 Could be. They won't know me! Tripping the light fantastic. 1 Camp Kare-free song. 7 Ballad of a social director. 11 Where did the night go? 4 Waiter's song. 6 Mix and mingle. 8 Shopping around. 17 Everybody love everybody. 20 Relax! 18 Don Jose of Far Rockaway. Everyone is lonely new version. Everyone is lonely. Glimpse of love. 23 Glimpse of love. (Wouldn't we make a) Charming couple. I hate to say goodnight. High and mighty - new. 2 High and mighty. 14 Look at me! 1 Opening. Having a wonderful time. Everyone is lonely final final version. Ooh what I done last night. Dancing! (to the thought of you). A bachelor's life. Men like a wolf already! Ain't nature grand. Certain individuals. Everybody love everybody. Flattery. Flattery old version. Flattery discarded. I had a glimpse of love. Wish you were here. Wish you were here. Wish you were here old version. Mix and mingle! Summer afternoon. 10 Tripping the light fantastic. 21 Who could eat now. Wish you were here. 2 You won't know me! I had to say goodnight (2nd version) discarded. When I think of you. Water under the bridge. 19 Wish you were here old discarded
    - [Wish you were here. Vocal score] Wish You Were Here / Musical Comedy by Arthur Kober and Joshua Logan; Music and Lyrics by Harold Rome; Orchestration by Don Walker. -- N.Y.: Chappell & Co., c1955., 1 vocal score (229 p.), bound; 31 cm. (Box 50, Folder 370-371, Box 51)
      Pl. no.: 4007-225
    - [Wish you were here. Vocal score] Wish you were here / A New Musical Comedy by Arthur Kober and Joshua Logan; Music and Lyrics by Harold Rome; Orchestrations by Don Walker., 1 manuscript vocal score (267 p.), bound; 36 cm. (Box 51, Folder 372)
      Labeled piano-conductor score, contains some orchestral cues
      Inscription from Jay Blackton and Mathilde on front fly leaf
      Contents: Overture. 1 Camp Kare-Free (Opening). 2 There's nothing nicer than people. 3 Ballad of a social director. 3A Incidental. 4 Shopping around. 5 Waiter's song. 7 Could be. 8 Mix and mingle - social hall. 9 Light fantastic. 10 Unsocial director. 11 Wish you were here - incidental. 12 Where did the night go? 13 Transition to athletic field. 14 Cue: "I'll show you how, pal." 15 Certain individuals. 16 Candlelight. 17 Chick's Hideaway. 17A Hideaway incidental. 18 Summer afternoon. 19 Finale - Act I. 20 Entr'acte. 20A Where did the night go (Opening - Act II). 21 Don Jose of Far Rockaway. 22 Everybody love everybody (Incidental + Song). 22A Everybody love everybody - dance. 23 Intro to Wish you were here. 24 Rain sequence. 25 Relax! 26 The dead pigeon. 27 Gone with the night bee-bop. 28 Camp Kare-Free - reprise. 29 Flattery. 30 They won't know me - reprise. 31 Finale - Act II. 32 Exit music.
    - [Wish you were here. Where did the night go: arr.] Where did the night go?: Fox-Trot From the New Musical Play "Wish you were here" / Words and Music by Harold Rome; Dance arr. by Johnny Warrington; Vocal backgrounds by Joe Leahy. -- N.Y.: Chappell & Co., Inc., c1952., 44 parts; 27 cm. (Box 51, Folder 373)
      Includes two sets of parts in keys for male and female vocals
    - [Wish you were here. Wish you were here; arr.] Wish you were here: Fox-Trot From the New Musical Play "Wish you were here" / Words and Music by Harold Rome; dance arr. by Johnny Warrington; vocal backgrounds by Joe Leahy. -- N.Y.: Chappell & Co., Inc., c1952., 48 parts; 27 cm. (Box 51, Folder 373)
      Includes two sets of parts for male and female vocals
    - [Wish you were here. Wish you were here; arr.] Wish you were here / Words and Music by Harold Rome; Arrangement for Orchestra by Jimmy Lally. -- Paris: Chappell S.A., c1953., 20 parts; 27 cm. (Box 51, Folder 373)
      Pl. no.: C.S.A. 3303-3304
      With: Where did the night go? (arr. for dance orchestra)
    - [Wonderful door. If you could read my mind (Sketches)], ca. 1966-1967; [3] p. of music; 31 cm. (Box 51, Folder 374)
      Lyrics ([7] sheets; 32 cm.) laid in
      Note on discarded folder: work sheets 1966-Mar. 1967 Wonderful Door / Southpaw
    - [Wonderful door (Sketches)], 1966 Mar.-Apr; [23] p. of music; 32 cm. (Box 51, Folder 375)
    - [Zulu and the zayda] The Zulu and the Zayda / Words + Music by Harold Rome., 1 manuscript score (25 p. in various pagings), bound; 32 cm. (Box 51, Folder 376)
      For voice with piano accompaniment and unaccompanied
      Contents: Rivers of tears. Aye-aye-aye. May your heart stay young (L'chayim). Oisgetzaichnet. Some things. Zulu love song. Tkambuza. Some things. Like the breeze blows
    - [Zulu and the zayda; arr.], 1965; 1 manuscript score (369 p. in various pagings) + 7 parts; 23 x 28-34 cm., 32 cm. (Box 52, Folder 377-387, Box 53)
      Manuscript (photocopy, in part originals) with pencil markings
      Arranged for instrumental ensemble
      Orchestrated by Meyer Kupferman? - several numbers bear his stamp dated 1965
      "Copying costs of Zulu and Zayda" and notes ([8] sheets; holographs in pencil and typescript) laid in
      Contents [in order according to the sheet labeled "Copying costs of Zulu and Zayda" - incomplete?]: Intro + Tkambuza (+trans.). 1A "Irish transition (2 copies). New "Gaelic" transition (original and copy). 3 Trans - Intro to Crocodile wife. #3 "Kishef" transition (2 copies). #4 "Herschel" transition (2 copies). 3B "Herschel" transition. #5 It's good to be alive. 4A Intro the "The water wears down the stone." 13B Transition to hospital garden. #7 Rivers of tears. 8 Transition to "Green meadows" (2 copies). 11 First act curtain (2 copies). 12 Some things. 13 Transition to Brothers (2 copies). 16 Transition to "Firing" scene (2 copies). 14 Transition to cemetery (2 copies). #16 Thank you Zayda. 19 The biggest men stumble (2 copies). 20 Harry seeks Paulus transition (2 copies). 21 Transition to hospital garden (2 copies). 22 "Good to be alive" reprise (2 copies). Transition + "Aye, aye, aye" (2 copies). Aye aye aye (on reverse: "Kishef" transition). Entre acte. Finale (original and bound copy)
    - [Zulu and the zayda. Selections], 1965 Jun.-Aug; 1 manuscript score ([74] p.); 32 cm. (Box 53, Folder 388)
      Includes sketches and lyrics ([23] sheets; holographs in pencil and typescript)
      Labeled "originals Zulu," some also labeled "discarded"
    - [Zulu and the zayda. Selections; arr.] The Zulu and The Zayda: Choral Selection for Mixed Chorus (S.A.T.B.) / Words and Music by Harold Rome; Arranged by Hale Smith. -- N.Y.: Florence Music Company, Inc., c1966., 1 chorus score (32 p.); 26 cm. (Box 53, Folder 389)
      For chorus (SATB), piano, and optional tambourine
      Pl. no.: 5680-31
    - [Zulu and the zayda. Selections; arr.], 30 parts; 17-35 cm. (Box 53, Folder 390)
      Grouped by musical number, each part counted
      Contents: Oisgetzaichnet. #1A "Irish" transition. Tikambuza. Transition + Aye aye aye (note on discarded envelope: Don Stewart from A Bl-? keep small score for me I'll return them to Meyer)
    - [Zulu and the zayda. Selections; arr.], 8 parts; 32-36 cm. (Box 53, Folder 391-392)
      Manuscript in ink and blue pencil (in part, photocopies)
      Includes woodwinds, percussion I-II, guitar, mandolin, violin, violoncello, and double bass parts
    - [Zulu and the zayda. Selections; arr.], [56] p. of music; 28-36 cm. (Box 53, Folder 393)
      Includes miscellaneous parts and sketches
  - Songs, I.B
    - [Ace of diamonds] Ace of diamonds / Harold Rome., 1 manuscript score ([2] p.); 32 cm. (Box 54, Folder 394)
    - [Advertising song] The advertising song (I believe!) / Music and Lyrics Harold Rome., 1 manuscript score (5 p.); 32 cm. (Box 54, Folder 394)
      Note on title page: As performed by Milton Berle in the Zigfield [sic] Follies
    - [After the fall] After the fall / Music + Lyrics Harold Rome. -- c1968., 1 manuscript score (2 sheets); 33 cm. (Box 54, Folder 394)
      Holograph, signed (photocopy)
    - [Ain't nature grand] Ain't nature grand! / Music + Lyrics Harold Rome., 1 manuscript score (3 p.); 32 cm. (Box 54, Folder 394)
    - [And so goodbye] And so goodbye / Harold Rome., 1 manuscript score ([2] p.); 32 cm. (Box 54, Folder 394)
    - [And so goodbye] And so goodbye / Harold Rome., 1 manuscript score ([2] p.); 32 cm. (Box 54, Folder 394)
    - [April will come again] April will come again / Music + Lyric by Harold J. Rome., 1 manuscript score (5 p.); 34 cm. (Box 54, Folder 394)
    - [Arouse, arouse!] Arouse! Arouse! / Harold Rome. -- 1968 Apr. 4., 1 manuscript score ([2] p.); 31 cm. (Box 54, Folder 394)
      Note: discarded
      Sketches ([3] p.) laid in
    - [Arouse, arouse!] Arouse, Arouse! / Music + Lyrics Harold Rome. -- 1968 Apr. 4., 1 manuscript score (3 p.); 31 cm. (Box 54, Folder 394)
      Note: dedicated to Sen. Eugene McCarthy
    - [Arouse, arouse!] Arouse, Arouse! / Lyrics and Music by Harold Rome. -- c1968., 1 manuscript score (3 sheets); 32 cm. (Box 54, Folder 394)
      Note: Dedicated to Sen. Eugene McCarthy
    - [Barbara] Barbara / Music + Lyrics Harold Rome. -- c1976., 1 manuscript score (3 p.); 30 cm. (Box 54, Folder 395)
      Note: For Barbara + Frank with Congrats
    - [Barbara (Sketches)] Barbara / Harold Rome. -- c1976., [2] p. of music; 32 cm. (Box 54, Folder 395)
    - [Be as good as you are] Be as good as you are / Harold Rome. -- 1958 Mar. 18., 1 manuscript score ([3] p.); 32 cm. (Box 54, Folder 395)
    - [Be as good as you are] Be as good as you are / Music + Lyrics Harold Rome. -- c1976., 1 manuscript score ([2] p.); 30 cm. (Box 54, Folder 395)
    - [Be as good as you are] Be as good as you are / Music + Lyrics Harold Rome. -- c1977., 1 manuscript score (2 p.); 32 cm. (Box 54, Folder 395)
      Photocopy laid in
    - [Boy rangers] Boy rangers / Music + Lyrics Harold Rome., 1 manuscript score (5 p.); 32 cm. (Box 54, Folder 395)
    - [Cab song. English; arr.] The cab song = (Le Fiacre): (The clip-clop song) / English Lyric by Harold Rome; Arr. by Walter Ehret; French Lyric and Music by Xandroff. -- N.Y.: Leeds Music Corporation, c1942., 1 chorus score (7 p.); 27 cm. (Box 54, Folder 396)
      Arranged for chorus (SSA) and piano
      Pl. no.: L1544-6
    - [Cheri] Cheri / Harold Rome., 1 manuscript score (3 p.); 32 cm. (Box 54, Folder 396)
    - [Cissy, Bertie and Joe] Cissy, Bertie + Joe: (Dead End Kids of Newspaper Row) / Music + Lyrics Harold Rome., 1 manuscript score (5 p.); 32 cm. (Box 54, Folder 396)
    - [Dangerous thoughts] Dangerous thoughts / Harold Rome., 1 manuscript score ([3] p.); 32 cm. (Box 54, Folder 396)